Well, so am I.
Could I interest
you in a nightcap?
I think that you could.
(Sheldon:)Leonard?
(Leonard:)What?
(Sheldon:)You realize you and I
could become brothers.
(Leonard:)We're not gonna be brothers.
(Leonard:)We're not gonna be stepbrothers.
(Leonard:)Go to sleep.
(Sheldon:)I hope you're right.
'Cause a grown man
living with his brother
(Sheldon:)and his brother's wife is weird.
(Leonard:)Go to sleep.
(Sheldon:)Okay.
(Sheldon:)Do you think your father's
doing unspeakable things
(Sheldon:)to my mother?
(Leonard:)No.
(Sheldon:)Are you saying that
(Sheldon:)because the things
are unspeakable?
Your parents are old.
Anything unspeakable
was finished by 9:30.
(Leonard:)Go to sleep.
(Sheldon:)Very well.
(Leonard:)I'm sorry if this stuff is gonna
make the ceremony awkward.
(Penny:)God, I thought my brother
fresh out of jail
(Penny:)was gonna make everyone
uncomfortable, but now this...
(Sheldon:)Hey, if you want me to sleep
(Sheldon:)you're gonna
have to stop talking.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪